Guide to the Doris Duke Audiovisual Collection, 1919-2012 and undated RL.10005
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audio, 1923-1989
  - Open reel audio tapes, 1950-1970; 128 items
    - Kitty White - Reel III, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001077001.wav)
      Includes songs Everything I've Got Belongs to You, I've Grown Accustomed to Your Face, Let Me Love You (three versions). Next to each song, Doris wrote whether song was Good or Fair.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0077)
    - Kitty, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001074001.wav)
      Includes songs "You Do Something to Me, Just In Time, Oh Do It Again (in C), Willow Weep For Me (B flat)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0074)
    - Kitty, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001075001.wav)
      Includes songs My Heart Belongs to Daddy, Party's Over, Do Nothing Till You Hear From Me (2 versions), Taking a Chance on Love
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0075)
    - Kitty, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001081001.wav)
      ? Blues
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0081)
    - Kitty, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001082001.wav)
      Includes songs Witchcraft, Happiness is Joe
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0082)
    - Kitty, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001083001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0083)
    - Kitty, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001084001.wav)
      Song titles handwritten on front are illegible.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0084)
    - Clover, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001076001.wav)
      Artist unknown. Includes songs Bossa Nova, Summer in the City, Say It Isn't So, Happiness is Just a Thing - Short Version (track only no vocal, no piano)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0076)
    - Joe Castro Orchestra, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001067001.wav;ddr001067002.wav;ddr001067003.wav)
      Contains three tracks. Track 1 is unknown singer presumably playing with the Joe Castro Orchestra. Sounds like it was recorded in a club. Songs include Ain't Misbehavin', Lady Be Good, More Than You Know, Boogie (instrumental), and Black Magic. Track 2 has a mixture of recordings including Middle Eastern or Indian music and man speaking in foreign language. Track 3 begins with man chanting, the switches to live recording of woman speaking to man in a foreign language. It sounds like they are in a public space.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0067)
    - Joe Castro Orchestra, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001128001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 46, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0128)
    - Les, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001043001.wav)
      Includes songs Fast Blues in C, Slow Waltz, ?, Lip Blues, Rock in G original
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0043)
    - Les, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001033001.wav)
      Includes songs (Fast) C blues ?, (Slow) Blues in F, Superman ?
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0033)
    - Les Me Lesson, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001047001.wav)
      Includes song But Not For Me. Other songs written on back of container are not legible.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0047)
    - Robert Banks, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001052001.wav;ddr001052002.wav)
      Includes songs Real 2x (Me), Didn't It Rain, I Have a Friend Above All Others, Open. Includes other songs, but handwriting is illegible.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0052)
    - Banks I, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001054001.wav)
      Includes songs Jesus is ? (Banks & me), Real (Banks), Lord Be With Me Where I Must Go, Jesus Wonderful Counselor, I Have a Friend, Rock My Lord, Lord I've Tried, Jesus is the ?, Holy Holy Holy
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0054)
    - Banks III, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001036001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0036)
    - Tracks - Robert Banks, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001053001.wav;ddr001053002.wav)
      Includes songs I Have But One God (B flat), Holding My Saviours Hand (G), That's Enough, Satisfied (B flat), Precious Lord (F), My Hope is ?, I Have Much to ?, Real, It Is No Secret, Didn't ?
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0053)
    - Practice with Banks and Lawrence, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001044001.wav)
      Includes songs Only a Look? and My Faith
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0044)
    - Oriental Delight, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001017001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0017)
    - Oriental Delight, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001018001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0018)
    - Oriental Delight, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001019001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0019)
    - Oriental Delight, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001020001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0020)
    - Me, undated
      Includes songs Day Tripper, Gone Medley, Like A Woman
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0101)
    - Me Willow, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001063001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0063)
    - Me It All Depends, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001059001.wav;ddr001059002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0059)
    - Misty Me, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001051001.wav;ddr001051002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0051)
    - Doris #2, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001058001.wav;ddr001058002.wav;ddr001058003.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0058)
    - Vocal exercises, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001055001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0055)
    - Reels 15 & 16?. Could also be Doris Duke Practice tape., undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001117001.wav)
      Track 15 includes waterfall over cave opening, water burbling fast stream, fast water over slope, water over slope - running little burbling. Track 16 includes chickens and cocks crowing, dogs barking, chickens and cocks. Also handwritten by Doris Duke on back cover is song Everytime I Feel the Spirit.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0117)
    - Look of Love / Midnight. Herbie & Me, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001064001.wav;ddr001064002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0064)
    - Aretha - Feel Good, Herbie & Me, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001061001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0061)
    - Herbie, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001032001.wav)
      Includes songs The Look of Love, Midnight Howl, Baby Baby Baby, Fool
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0032)
    - Rev Roberts Church, 1970 February 5 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001016001.wav)
      Edited seminar tape. Feb. 5 1970 Leavenworth Pentecostal Church 801 5th Ave.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0016)
    - Rev II, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001056001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0056)
    - Louis Bromfield, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001008001.wav;ddr001008002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0008)
    - Highways, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001023001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0023)
    - Dunham Drums, undated
      On the reel itself handwritten label reads "Dunham ? Piano ? Music
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0024)
    - Virginia, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001026001.wav;ddr001026002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0026)
    - Time Won't Be No More, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001027001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0027)
    - Bernie, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001029001.wav)
      Includes songs In the Still of the Night, Day Tripper, You've Lost that Lovin' Feeling, I Think I'm Going Out of My Head, Reach Up for Me ?
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0029)
    - Oscar Peterson, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001031001.wav;ddr001031002.wav)
      Blues
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0031)
    - Everett Gordon, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001035001.wav;ddr001035002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0035)
    - An?g. Choir, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001038001.wav;ddr001038002.wav)
      Out of Zion
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0038)
    - Connie, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001039001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0039)
    - Indiana, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001041001.wav)
      On back of container Doris Duke wrote following: Breaks - Art, ? - Me (RH, both, LH), Art - ? (fast)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0041)
    - Trio, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001042001.wav)
      Includes songs Let It Be Me, Just Closer Walk With Thee, A Natural Woman, I Told You So, You Send Me, I Heard the Voice of Jesus
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0042)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001045001.wav;ddr001045002.wav)
      Includes songs Keep on Walking (in A flat), Keep ? to Cross (in A flat), Walking Piano (in A flat), Jesus Brings Things (in A flat), Pass Me Not Gentle Savior (in A flat), Be Patient with Me, I Am Sacred (in A flat), Shout He Lives, Jesus I Feel All Right (in B flat), Who Made the Mountain
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0045)
    - Delhi Exercises, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001046001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0046)
    - Nadia Gamal Dances, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001048001.wav)
      Includes Sacalonee ? Alf Leila Leila, Douse ?
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0048)
    - Nick Practice Tape, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001049001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0049)
    - Any Rivers, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001057001.wav)
      Includes songs Any Rivers, Chorus, and Sparrow
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0057)
    - Ew Vocalizes, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001060001.wav;ddr001060002.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0060)
    - So Long, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001062001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0062)
    - Various, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001068001.wav;ddr001068002.wav)
      Includes songs Lush Life (Joe), Call Me Irresponsible (Kitty), Laura (Nat Cole), Don't Blame Me (Nat Cole)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0068)
    - Mr. Robert Braheem Farrah, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001087001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0087)
    - Synclavier at 50 percent at 100 percent, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001090001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0090)
    - Reel 44, 1967 July 21 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001115001.wav)
      Recorded at Tahiti Hotel. ? Group - slowest tempos.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0115)
    - Reel 42, 1967 July 21 (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001119001.wav)
      Includes Tahiti Hotel Group, Marie, Maori Song
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 41, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0119)
    - Georgia / Sue, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001001001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0001)
    - Uphill Journey 7 1/2 Stereo, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001002001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0002)
    - Cleveland Oss, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001003001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0003)
    - Aretha-Ray Spirit in the Dark, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001005001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0005)
    - Blank, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001086001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0086)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001050001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0050)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001007001.wav)
      Includes 12 songs: Mellowtone, Like a Woman, Goody Goody, Autumn Leaves, Rock Medley, You Do Something to Me, Misty Roses, Let's Do It, Unchain My Heart, Gone Medley, It All Depends on You, I Love Jazz
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0007)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0085)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001088001.wav)
      Contents of tape are handwritten on back, but are illegible.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0088)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001040001.wav)
      Unchain My Heart. Reel was shipped from B. Hoffer in New York to Sydney Shaw in care of Johnny Gomez at the Shangri La residence.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 39, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0040)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0091)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0092)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0093)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0094)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001095001.wav)
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0095)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001096001.wav)
      "G" written in marker on reel
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0096)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001097001.wav)
      "3" written on tape on front cover.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0097)
    - Unknown, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0098)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001099001.wav)
      "5" written on tape on front cover.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0099)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials RL10005-SET-0005, Audio-file ddr001100001.wav)
      "6" written on tape on front cover.
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 40, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0100)
    - Sonic Solutions, No Noise & Lexicon 2400, undated
      - Original quarter-inch open-reel audio tape (Box 38, Audio-reel RL10005-RR-0022)
  - Audiocassettes, 1974-1989; 48 items
    This subseries consists of audiocassettes which are a mix of original and commercial recordings. The original recordings are primarily of gospel artists and groups, including the Cleveland Church Choir and High Point Choir, which reflects Doris' interest in gospel music. Also included are live recordings of the Newport Jazz Festival. The commercial audiocassettes are primarily of a spiritual nature from the Self-Realization Church. Of particular interest is a presumed telephone interview with Howard Hughes conducted in the early 1970s and a live recording of the inaugural flight of the Spruce Goose in 1947.
    - Edward Tabela. A High Price for Love, 1973 December (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0018_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0018_02_pm.wav)
      Cassette tape sent to Doris Duke from Edward Tabela, who was asking for Doris Duke to support him financially. All the parts of the melodrama are acted out by Mr. Tabela. Correspondence from Mr. Tabela to Doris Duke is in Box 377 of the Doris Duke Papers.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0018)
    - LL Blues and untitled recording, 1973 April 11 (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0043_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0043_02_pm.wav)
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0043)
    - Is Meditation on God Compatible with Modern Life? An Informal Talk by Sri Daya Mata on the Teachings of Paramahansa Yogananda, 1974
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0028)
    - Doris Duke - New Jersey Robbery (Side 1 and 2), 1974 February 23 (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0003_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0003_02_pm.wav)
      Two unknown men and woman speaking in low tones; most of the time barely audible. Sounds like they are investigating the robbery at Duke Farms and recorded it while working through the details/interviewing people.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0003)
    - Doris Duke - New Jersey Robbery (Side 3 and 4), 1974 February 23 (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0004_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0004_02_pm.wav)
      Continuation of RL10005-CS-0003.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0004)
    - Doris Duke - New Jersey Robbery (Side 5 and 6), 1974 February 23 (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0005_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0005_02_pm.wav)
      Continuation of RL10005-CS-0004.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0005)
    - A Heart Aflame. An Informal Talk by Sri Daya Mata on the Teachings of Paramahansa Yogananda., 1977
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0026)
    - Renee Geyer, 1982
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0020)
    - Jane Pickens Hoving. Songs From The Heart, 1984
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0022)
    - Vadana. Indian Devotional Chants. Self-Realization Church, 1984
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0037)
    - Newport 84. Dizzy and Ray Charles, 1984[?] (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0002_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0002_02_pm.wav)
      Presumably a live recording of the Newport Jazz Festival from 1984; includes artists Dizzy Gillespie and Ray Charles. Can hear people chatting and clapping in the background.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0002)
    - Beholding the One in All. An informal talk by Paramahansa Yogananda., 1985
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0038)
    - Awake in the Cosmic Dream. An informal talk by Paramahansa Yogananda, 1987
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0031)
    - Luigi Zaninelli. Songs from the Magic Place, 1989
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0033)
    - Altshuler/NYU Project, undated (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0001_01_pm.wav)
      Essentially a pitch for financial support for bringing the Robert and John Altman jazz collection of 500,000 master pressings to NYU.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0001)
    - Herbert R. Denis Jr., undated (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0006_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0006_02_pm.wav)
      Likely copy of a commercial recording. Contemporary music sung in French.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0006)
    - Africa[?], undated (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0007_01_pm.wav)
      Side 1 only. Sounds like a live recording. Primarily [African?] drumming with some chanting and musical instruments in the background.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0007)
    - Unknown, undated (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0008_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0008_02_pm.wav)
      Side 1 includes various people singing spiritual songs accompanied by piano. Side 2 appears to be vocal lessons for Doris Duke. Also includes unknown man and woman singing spiritual songs.
      - Original audiocassette (Box 35, Audio-cassette RL10005-CS-0008)
    - BB King, undated (Digital-materials SET-0006, Audio-file RL10005CS0009_01_pm.wav; RL10005CS0009_02_pm.wav)